A Watan Pratham list of market people who are going to
talk, I will tell you the complete justice about ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Company's quarter for kids,
what is the company's
official result, has it declared any dividend, or
not, study updates from the
company, share it, I will pick up the full phone,
then subscribe to the channel made in the video,
if you have
turned on Telegram channels, then check its link
in the description, to that hotspot
of latest updates of Telegram channels, you
can join, let me
tell you a little more about the company, the company
is India's most logistic general insurance company, in different segments, when
other companies, health related, property related,
motors related, fire related and
many more segmented companies, it
provides event, a medium sized different
companies, due to its market, the
company's market is 6270 thousand crores, so before I
tell you about the dividend, so before the water phone
result, I
want to tell you a little more information which is
event related and Azhar  If you want to
see the updates then first of all the company
declared a dividend of ₹5 per share
in the March 2022 quarter ended chilli and the
interesting thing is that in the last
continuous quarter maths means
from 2021 to 2022 which is financial, in that
in every quarter the company deleted delete or
matched it with diploma student that
in August also chop balmu this is just waterproof to
water three skipping almost the company
regularly depends, if I
tell a stranger then the company told that the
company is one of their
general employees who is going to do this aircraft in the board of directors,
apart from that the
main income of the company in dross premium is a good
village, the
income of the company from village is Rahu solvency rate, that too
point 6 pack good time from Solan, the global
company had maintained the result of
water for, tell me the result of March 2022
which is quarter for end there the company tax
463 likes in total income, the
gross income of this company is increased and the blood relative of premium is
increased the total income pin great
for a quarter opposite 20% friend and this
visit 33 likes correct but the company had to make some
provisions some expenses also
increased so the expenses in quarter 20 are
one crore use on this
small likes this effect because of
provisions and co successful and tractor company's
net profit up and down line surj revenue
total has been seen still the net
profit is 30 crore fit in the
quarter in which phone 1500 had
posted a net profit of 36 crore from
there it makes a
net profit of 330 crore so
subscribe
yes this is what is happening that the provisions that are being made, the
claim settlements that are happening, somewhere the
company is not able to make that much
profit, if we
talk about the city, the
cigarette sales of the company are around IPL 2017  So
sure, the company's share doubled in 3 years.
Sure, in the last few years,
many different back pains were
not able to perform,
where health related, game related, many
companies were not able to perform, that
company's share and the
subscribers going to the market are definitely very high and
along with that, competition, so all these will take
time, so
keep it below the photo, through butter, you can
expect Vikram, so this is that type of stock,
so a body invest, this is such a number
district chilli, then definitely you
can stay invested, so point of youth into various
potential apps to double your money here, so this was the complete
information about the same but quiet officer,
if you liked the video, then
like the video, if you have any query, then definitely
tell in the comment section and
thanks for watching and thank you.